<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.program.steamlink" name="Steamlink" version="0.0.2" provider-name="meekys">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="service.system.docker" optional="true" version="9.80.11.133"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="addon.py">
        <provides>game</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Launcher for Steamlink game streaming on LibreELEC Raspberry Pi and Generic x86_64 devices.</summary>
        <summary lang="nl_NL">Starter voor Steamlink game streaming voor LibreELEC Raspberry Pi en generieke x86_64 apparaten.</summary>
        <summary lang="de_DE">Starter für Steamlink-Spiel-Streaming für LibreELEC Raspberry Pi und generischen x86_64-Geräten.</summary>
        <summary lang="fr_FR">Lanceur pour Steamlink pour les appareils LibreELEC Raspberry Pi et appareils génériques en x86_64.</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">This add-on launches Steamlink. This add-on also has the ability to update Steamlink.</description>
        <description lang="nl_NL">Deze uitbreiding start Steamlink. Deze uitbreiding heeft ook de mogelijkheid om een specifiek spel op te starten en Steamlink bij te werken.</description>
        <description lang="de_DE">Diese Erweiterung startet Steamlink. Diese Erweiterung bietet auch die Möglichkeit, ein bestimmtes Spiel zu starten und Steamlink zu aktualisieren.</description>
        <description lang="fr_FR">Cet add-on lance Steamlink. Cet add-on permet aussi de lancer un jeu directement et de mettre à jour Steamlink.</description>
        <language>en nl de fr</language>
        <platform>linux</platform>
        <license>GPL-3.0-or-later</license>
        <website>https://github.com/meekys/plugin.program.steamlink</website>
        <source>https://github.com/meekys/plugin.program.steamlink</source>
        <news>
v0.0.2
- Fixes for LibreELEC 12 and Raspberry Pi 4/5
v0.0.1
- Initial release for LibreELEC on the Raspberry Pi 4
        </news>
        <disclaimer lang="en_GB">Feel free to use this at your own risk.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="nl_NL">Voel je vrij om dit te gebruiken maar wel op eigen risico.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="de_DE">Sie können dies auf eigenes Risiko verwenden.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Utilisez cet add-on à vos risques et périls.</disclaimer>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
            <banner>resources/banner.png</banner>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot.png</screenshot>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
